(Sheldon:)Alex, check my schedule.
What does my afternoon look like?
(Alex:)I think it's pretty wide open. Oh, wait.
Here's something at 4:00.
"Give Alex a talking to"?
(Sheldon:)Well, that snuck up on us, didn't it?
- Is there a problem?
- Let's not call it a problem...
(Sheldon:)...let's call it an opportunity.
(Sheldon:)To solve a serious problem.
(Alex:)What did I do?
(Sheldon:)You don't know? Oh, you poor dear.
(Sheldon:)Your ovaries are squirting so much
goofy juice into your brain...
...you don't know which way is up.
(Sheldon:)You made an inappropriate
sexual advance towards Dr. Hofstadter.
(Alex:)What? I didn't make a sexual advance
on anybody.
(Sheldon:)Now, there's no need to get defensive.